DAWID WIJATA

Fullstack .NET Developer

Fullstack Developer with 2 years in the industry, working with professionals from a variety of disciplines. Driven by implementing solutions that are meaningful and bring income to others. Already worked in 4 software development projects for automotive and financial companies. Interested in frontend architecture and micro frontends concept.

Contact information

Mail address: contact@dawidwijata.pl
Phone number: +48 882 622 209
GitHub profile: github.com/BordowyRydwan
Location: Warsaw, Poland

LinkedIn profile: linkedin.com/in/dawid-wijata/

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2019 - 2023

Faculty of Applied Informatics and Mathematics Warsaw University of Life Sciences

Specialization Information System Engineering

Thesis Comparison of Microfrontend Applications and Monolith Frontend Applications Based on the

Example of Expense Tracker

Work experience

Fullstack .NET Developer, KPMG Poland

09.2022 - present

- maintained a large-scaled tax calculation software named KTax, that is officially accredited to calculate taxes and deductions in three Swiss cantons
- developed 10+ new features to adjust the Swiss tax law requirements from FY 2023
- optimized the loading speed of a project page in the tax calculation software by 80%
- cooperated with a team of 5 people, sticking to Agile management approach, in order to fulfill the business needs
- implemented the backend, frontend and set up the architecture of KVideo service for 100+ videos that supports
 the client's company onboarding and internal training processes
- implemented unit, integration and behavioral tests, leading to up to 90% code coverage

Fullstack Developer, Atinea Sp. z o.o.

05.2021 - 08.2022

- migrated an API of enterprise application from VBA to REST-based one with ASP.NET
- used Entity Framework Core for accessing and modeling SQL Server database
- designed a frontend application using micro frontends concept with Single SPA and Angular 12
- conducted a code review process multiple times in a team of 5 developers
- designed an architecture of a WPF-based guard application project for company internal code challenge
- led a small team of 2 developers during a process of implementation of a WPF-based guard application
- analyzed and planned a set of features supporting client's company complaint management process

Skills

- frontend development with Angular, RxJs, TypeScript, JavaScript
- C#, .NET Framework, .NET Core, ASP.NET, Entity Framework
- designing REST API; API documentation with Swagger and NSwag
- relational databases SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle SQL
- using Git versioning system with Azure DevOps, BitBucket and GitHub
- Docker and Kubernetes basics
- maintaining clean code, using design and architectural patterns, working with Agile management approach
- unit and integration testing with nUnit, xUnit, Karma, Jest, Jasmine, behavioral testing with Specflow

Languages: Polish - native, English - C1

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).